<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Chris Turner</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Chris Turner</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The Bee Movie Script</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/11/test-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/11/test-post/</guid>
      <description>You like jazz? Pixar, please don&#39;t copyright strike me.
 According to all known laws of aviation,
there is no way a bee should be able to fly.
Its wings are too small to get its fat little body off the ground.
The bee, of course, flies anyway
because bees don&#39;t care what humans think is impossible.
Yellow, black. Yellow, black. Yellow, black. Yellow, black.
Ooh, black and yellow! Let&#39;s shake it up a little.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Reticulate: Using R Studio and Python Together</title>
      <link>/post/2020/12/10/reticulate-using-r-studio-and-python-together/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Dec 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/2020/12/10/reticulate-using-r-studio-and-python-together/</guid>
      <description>Working with Reticulate If you didn&#39;t know, the reticulated python is one of the longest and heaviest snakes found in Southeast and South Asia. It&#39;s a bit hard to handle in captivity due to the fact that it does what it&#39;s known to do: be a snake that likes to kill stuff. Look at this cutie!
 However, there is no such thing as a &amp;quot;reticulated R&amp;quot; in the wild.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 2: Modeling, Testing, and Predicting</title>
      <link>/project/project2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project2/</guid>
      <description>Noor Khan - nk8455 Introduction In this project, I will be looking at the dataset ResumeNames in order to determine if different variables will affect you receiving a call back from a job you applied to. I chose this dataset because it deals with racism in the workplace; I wanted to answer whether one&#39;s ethnicity had an impact on them getting a job and by how much. Although the original dataset has 27 different variables, I decided to select 12 of the ones I think have the greatest effect in order to fit the rubric guidelines.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Project 1: Exploratory Data Analysis</title>
      <link>/project/project1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/project1/</guid>
      <description>Noor Khan - nk8455 Introduction The two datasets chosen for this project was US Hate Crime Data and us_rent_income in order to determine if there is a relationship between the state&#39;s median rent and income and different types of hate crimes. In US Hate Crime Data, there is a count of the different types of hate crimes in each state in 2017. In us_rent_income, there are the estimated values of the median yearly income and the median monthly rent of each state in 2017 along with the 90% margin of error.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Projects</title>
      <link>/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/</guid>
      <description> Check out some of my coding projects below:
 Wrangling &amp;amp; Exploratory Data Analysis
 Modeling, Inference, Prediction
  -- </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resume</title>
      <link>/resume/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/resume/</guid>
      <description>For more information, contact me though my e-mail.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
